
# questions = [
#     {
#         "prompt": "Which of the Mario games came first?",
#         "answers": [
#             "1: Super Mario Odyssey",
#             "2: Super Mario Run",
#             "3: Mario Bros",
#             "4: New Super Mario Bros"
#         ],
#         "correct": "3"
#     },
#     {
#         "prompt": "In which game did Mario first appear?",
#         "answers": [
#             "1: Ice Climber",
#             "2: Donkey Kong",
#             "3: The Legend of Zelda",
#             "4: Kid Icarus"
#         ],
#         "correct": "2"
#     },
#     {
#         "prompt": "In which year was the Super Mario Bros film released?",
#         "answers": [
#             "1: 1993",
#             "2: 2001",
#             "3: 2007",
#             "4: There is no film"
#         ],
#         "correct": "1"
#     },
#     {
#         "prompt": "What was Mario's original name?",
#         "answers": [
#             "1: Spanner Dude",
#             "2: Paolo",
#             "3: Jumpman",
#             "4: Fabio"
#         ],
#         "correct": "3"
#     },
#     {
#         "prompt": "What kind of job did Mario do before plumbing?",
#         "answers": [
#             "1: Carpenter",
#             "2: Baker",
#             "3: Dentist",
#             "4: Poet"
#         ],
#         "correct": "1"
#     },
#     {
#         "prompt": "What handedness is Link in most games?",
#         "answers": [
#             "1: Right",
#             "2: Left"
#         ],
#         "correct": "2"
#     },
#     {
#         "prompt": "What does the old man give Link in Breath of the Wild?",
#         "answers": [
#             "1: A bow and arrows",
#             "2: Bad advice",
#             "3: Baked apples",
#             "4: Breakable armor"
#         ],
#         "correct": "3"
#     },
#     {
#         "prompt": "In Breath of the Wild, where is Spectacle Rock found?",
#         "answers": [
#             "1: Great plateau",
#             "2: Tal Tal Mountain Ridge",
#             "3: Forest of Time",
#             "4: Gerudo Region"
#         ],
#         "correct": "4"
#     },
#     {
#         "prompt": "How many Legend of Zelda games feature Link in the Title?",
#         "answers": [
#             "1: 3",
#             "2: 4",
#             "3: 5",
#             "4: 6"
#         ],
#         "correct": "2"
#     },
#     {
#         "prompt": "What is the main part of a Goron's diet?",
#         "answers": [
#             "1: Rocks",
#             "2: Rubies",
#             "3: Rats",
#             "4: Rubber plants"
#         ],
#         "correct": "1"
#     }
# ]

# with open('questions.json', 'w') as file:
#     json.dump(questions, file, indent = 4)

